http://www.paystation.co.nz/information-pages/terms-of-use/

Customised payment options
Multi-site payments (MOTO chain and chain batch)
Fully hosted (3 party)
Merchant hosted (2 party)
Providing a refund
How to save card details for future payments (tokens)
Customised payment options
Multi-site payments (MOTO chain and chain batch)
Fully hosted (3 party)
Merchant hosted (2 party)
Terms Of Use
Terms & ConditionsAcceptanceThis is the official website of Paystation Limited. By accessing our site you agree to our terms of access listed below.General disclaimerThe content on our site is for information only. While we try to ensure that the content of our site is free from error, we do not warrant its accuracy, adequacy or completeness or its suitability for your intended use. The content on our site is not intended to be a substitute for commercial judgement or professional advice, and you should not act in reliance upon any of our site's content, without first obtaining professional advice relevant to your circumstances.How we use your informationWhen transmitting your personal information over the Internet, you should remember that the Internet is not a secure environment. Any personal information you transmit to Paystation Limited may be used by Paystation Limited to provide information to you about the full range of products and services offered by Paystation Limited and as provided for in our privacy policy.LiabilityWe disclaim, to the extent permitted by law, all liability or responsibility to anyone for any direct or indirect loss or damage that may result from the action or failure to act by anyone in reliance on the content of our website.Changes to contentAll content on this site (including these terms of access) is subject to change at any time.Jurisdiction Unless otherwise specified, the content on this site has been prepared in accordance with New Zealand law for the supply of products and services to persons resident in New Zealand only. The content of this website and any contracts formed with Paystation Limited arising out of this site are governed by New Zealand law and New Zealand Courts have jurisdiction.LinksPlease contact Paystation Limited for prior permission if you wish to create a hypertext link to any page on this Paystation Limited Website. If you create a link to the Paystation Limited Website, you remain fully responsible for any consequences of that link, whether direct or indirect and you will protect Paystation Limited against all loss, damage, liability, costs or expense arising from or in connection with the link. Paystation Limited accepts no responsibility or liability in relation to any content on other websites that are not under our direct control.Privacy policyAny information you transmit to us may be used by us, to, amongst other things, advise you of our products and services or as otherwise described in our privacy policy. In certain situations, we may be obliged to disclose information to law enforcement or other government agencies, for example in the event of an investigation into any activity that is illegal, or that may expose us to legal liability. You have the right to access and correct your personal information held by Paystation Limited subject to the provisions of the Privacy Act 1993.CopyrightThe content of our site is protected by copyright and no part of our site may be reproduced or adapted in whole or in part without our prior consent.
Back to Top
Information pages
Copyright
Links
Terms Of Use
Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Pricing
